The different sounds are awesome.
It's so much fun!
Can you go a little more?
It's so beautiful!
Amazing!
It's so amazing!
That's amazing.
Oh, my gosh.
Hello.
I'm Mana Takase from Hyuhizaka 46.
Where am I today?
I'm here at Drone School Odaiba.
The reason why I'm here is...
I wanted to start something new.
I've started to use a drone.
I've started using a drone to take pictures of our members.
I want to take pictures of beautiful scenery.
I think I need to take some visual shots to do that.
I would like to come to this drone school in Odaiba and learn many things.
I came here to learn various things.
Yay!
Let's get started!
Wow!
That's great!
Hi, I'm Mana Takase from Hyugaizaka 46.
Pleased to meet you.
Difficult to take a selfie.
There are actually areas where the misery of drones is prohibited by national certification
Actually, the national certification just started last December.
There's a first and second class of national certification.
And that you can get a person to person permit.
The difference is that you will continue to be allowed to work in the private sector.
If you obtain National Qualification 2, you can
A person, an object, or a drone at a distance of 30 meters.
If you are a joke in a populated area
If you are married to a person who is married to a person who is married to a person who is married to a person
People who are out of sight and at night
This one is just to have a license
You don't need to apply to fly it.
I see.
Yes, sir.
You have a lot of energy, don't you?
Yes, I do. I bought this drone myself, and tannie Plus One, a drone entertainer, gave it to me,
Do you have a specific practice drone that you use to take comparisons?
There are certain conditions, so today I will lend you a drone from my school.
Thank you very much.
I'll try to fly it. Let's go.
Oh, I can do it.
Wow, I'm going to try to put a loop through it. I'll use the top loop.
Got it.
You were very good at piloting the terror.
Really?
Let's use a bigger drone.
Let's practice with a larger drone and actually change the direction of the drone.
This one?
This is it.
Suddenly it looks really serious!
This drone is actually used for the national certification course and
This drone is also used for the exam.
This is the left stick up lever.
You have to put it in softly and raise it.
First of all, please raise it to eye level.
Oh! The sound is different! The sound is amazing!
But it's great! I don't know what it is, but it's very stable.
Yes, the GPS line is picking it up now, so it has an adaptive feature!
Wow!
First, please move sideways to the red mat on the right.
Uh-oh.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Next, please move horizontally to the left to the red mat on the left.
It's so much fun.
Let's land in the middle.
Let's go back to the middle of the stage.
We're going to land with the left stick.
We're going to put the style on the bottom.
Press and hold all the way down on the stage.
Yes, sir.
You're a very fast learner.
Really?
I just told you a little bit about it, but it's flying so beautifully now.
You're so good with compliments!
I'm glad.
That's a relief.
It's actually part of the national certification.
I'd like you to move your qualification while changing the direction of the aircraft.
First of all, I'd like you to change the direction of the aircraft to point A here.
Move to point A.
Now I'd like you to change the direction of the aircraft from point A to point B.
I want you to move forward.
Point B, point C, and point D at the back.
Point E on the left front.
Yes, we've asked you to circle back around while changing the direction of the plane.
Now let's go to the square plane.
Please rise to eye level.
Let's go up to square plane height.
Put it in sideways and turn it.
Oh!
Oh, is it showing? - Is it showing?
Are you seeing this?
Okay, I'm going to need you to move up to Line A, please.
Yes, sir.
Almost there.
Okay.
I'd like you to turn from line A to line B.
Move with your whole body, please.
Yes, sir.
Like this.
Straight ahead.
Yes, sir.
I'm tempted to turn around.
I know.
I want to look in the same direction.
Maybe a little more.
Could you please type to the left?
Yes, sir.
Turn the plane from point B to point C and move.
Oh smooth
Yes, sir.
How was it?
Well, it was a shame that we had to stop in some places along the way.
The only other thing is that we need to make sure that the aircraft is facing the right direction before proceeding.
If you are careful, there will be no problem.
I see.
Next is the actual flight on the 8!
Wow, it looks really difficult!
I'm going to move it a little bit.
If you move it forward, it will turn around and if you move it to the left, it will turn around.
You need to do both.
If you stop, you lose points.
You have to keep doing it.
Like this.
At the same time?
Yes, you have to move forward and turn around, and then turn around and do it all at the same time.
If you move out to the right, or if you move across the middle cone, you are out of the origin at that point.
At that point, it will be a square, so let's be careful.
Let's be careful.
Let's start with the right circle and then move to the left circle.
It's going to be very slow.
Very slowly.
Yes, I want to go around.
Touring.
Let's go to the left pearl.
This way.
Let's turn it a little bit.
With the previous input.
Turn the limit as you turn it.
GaN WE are Hiroga's
It's our first time.
Thank you for your help with my first delivery car.
But maybe there wasn't much of a save picture book.
For the first time
It was my first time to be taken care of by a delivery truck!
But I'm glad we didn't hit any bumps and got back safely.
There's a part at the end where there's an anomaly.
Now it stays in place on its own, even if you don't touch it.
It's been doing this for a while now.
But now the sensor is going to turn off.
If you don't touch the stick, it won't stay there.
It won't stay in place unless I touch the stick.
That's going to be difficult.
That's the hardest part.
It's like this.
It's wobbly.
It's moving on its own.
You have to keep your thumb on the stick the whole time.
If it goes down, you have to pull it back up.
You have to have a fine charm.
First things first.
Let's practice to stay in the circle.
Yes, sir.
If it goes out of place, put it back in.
Surprisingly, I'm fine.
Not bad.
Oh...
It's like the time of year and these practicals together will determine if you pass.
You start with 100 points, and if you have more than 70 points, you pass.
By the way, I just did three items.
Can you give me a score for the three items I just did?
Okay, let's do it.
I'm so nervous.
Let's get started.
Okay.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm getting really serious.
Emotionless versus derivative.
Please continue to take it.
Thank you for watching.
Overall, we've deducted a little over 10 points from the total.
We don't have a little less than 10 minus points, so you start with 100 points.
Minus 13 points, so we have 87 points left.
Good.
That's a good start for day one.
Thank you very much.
Rainbow Bridge?
Rainbow Bridge.
Oh, there's a string on it, just in case it goes away.
Can I go as far up as this string will go?
It can go as far as it can go.
I don't know how many meters it is now, but it's like 3 meters.
It's a little more than that.
Can you go a little further?
What?
It's so beautiful.
Wow!
Wow.
I'm afraid you're looking at the wrong guy.
This is what Mr. Takase is filming right now.
It's so beautiful!
If you put the lever on the left tic to change the direction of the drone
The drone will move in a circular motion.
Wow, it's amazing!
It's amazing, because it's from a point of view that you can't see.
It's amazing. It's very impressive.
It's very impressive.
How does it feel to fly outside for the first time?
It's such a beautiful view.
It makes me want to fly even farther.
It feels great, doesn't it?
It feels really good.
Home point, please.
This is difficult.
I don't know how far I should go.
It's all a feeling, isn't it?
It's a feeling, too.
The deeper you go and the higher you go, the more difficult it gets.
The higher you go, the more difficult it becomes to understand.
The more you practice, the harder it will be to understand.
You'll be able to cultivate it.
That felt good.
Right in the middle.
I learned a lot about drones today.
I really learned a lot.
I'm going to work really hard to achieve my dreams
I'm really going to work hard to achieve my various dreams.
I'll do my best!
This is Mana Takase.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
See you soon!
Bye bye!